NURHAMSAH

Fullstack Developer

Indonesia, Jawa Timur, Kediri, Mojo 64162 0812-1322-1343

nur.hamsah.cash@gmail.com

https://nurhamsah.vercel.app/

@NURHAMSAH_TECH

SUMMARY

a professional software developer and has quite a lot of experience building projects with a great team. Very proficient in using the React / Next js framework and always prioritizes code performance, security and user experience to achieve amazing results.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Feedloop - Jakarta, Indonesia

Frontend developer (Apr 2023 - Apr 2024)

- Integration unit test using Jest / React testing library
- Debugging
- · Create advanced features
- · Daily / weekly meeting
- · Convert figma to code
- · Team work

Freelance - Kediri, Indonesia

Fullstack developer (Nov 2022 - Nov 2023)

- · Create dynamic student bills
- · Role management
- · Security authentication
- · Management student (Grade, Bill report, Account, ect.)

Code Art Online - Tulungagung, Indonesia

Frontend developer (Dec 2021 - Feb 2023)

- · Integration unit test using cypress
- · Working on various application features from clients
- · Convert figma to code
- Improvment feature cashier mobile app
- · Weekly meeting
- Team work

EDUCATION

SMK PGRI KRAS - Kediri, Indonesia (2014 - 2017)

Computer and network engineer

PERSONAL PROJECT

Mini Restaurant App

https://github.com/nurhamsah1998/Restaurant

Bertanya App

https://bertanya.vercel.app/

Todo Premium App

https://todo-premium.vercel.app/

CERTIFICATE

Laravel Web Development (May 02 - Jun 23, 2023)

PKS Digital School

No. 6162/PKS/DigiS/VI/2023

https://member.pksdigitalschool.id/sertifikat/generate/b66f9455-9ef5-4020-928b-6e18923a8470

SKILLS

- HTML, CSS, SCSS
- JavaScript, TypeScript
- PHP

Figma

Git

- React JS
- Github, Gitlab
- Redux, Jotai
- Jest, Cypress
- REST API
- Node JS
- Firebase
- Sequelize (mysql)

Supabase

React Native

Next JS

- Laravel